♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Somewhere in time and space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson and
his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in a nasty place ♪
♪ They try to survive
the wrath of Pearl ♪
♪ Just an evil gal who
wants to rule the world ♪
♪ From her castle below,
she sets her sights above ♪
♪ Just to torture all
her captives on the
Satellite of Love ♪
- [Mike] Get me down!
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
- You're on!
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Oh my stars!
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- Check me out!
♪ Croooow ♪
- I'm different!
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(guitar twanging)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
(humming)
- Oh hey Mike, I see you've
got today's Boston Globe.
- Yeah, Crow.
I didn't know you had
a syndicated column
in the lifestyle section
of many major newspapers.
- Oh sure.
I was inspired by Larry
King's column in USA Today.
- "My Two Cents,"
by Crow T. Robot.
- Yeah.
- "I said it before
and I'll say it again.
Shoelaces are handy,
even necessary
to many of today's shoe styles."
- Yeah.
- "Volleyball player
Gabrielle Reece
is the best athlete in
the world, in arguably
the most difficult
of all sports."
- Right.
- "The Boeing 727 is still
my favorite aircraft.
I give Supreme Court Justice
Antonin Scalia a B-plus."
- Yup.
- "Television shows
aired last night."
Crow, I have to say, this column
doesn't seem
particularly substantive.
- Oh, thanks Mike.
You should have seen
last Tuesday's column.
I remarked on a patty
melt I had for lunch.
- That's fascinating.
Now who reads this column?
- Well, you for one.
- Crow, you are right
on about shoelaces, man.
I don't know what
we'd do without
journalists like you
telling it like it is.
- We'll be right back.
- Wow, television shows
did air last night!
(instrumental theme music)
- Okay Mike, is this
more substantial?
Could there be more goose
poop in my front yard?
- No.
- No, it's not more substantial,
or no, there could not be
more goose poop in my...
- Let's see what
Pearl's up to, okay?
- I just wanted an answer.
(thunder crashing)
- Huh?
- What the?
- Hey! Hey, look at
this, another button.
- I never noticed
that before. Hello?
- Oh, hi Mike. I'm sorry.
I should have told you we
were moving the castle.
I didn't mean to
leave you home alone.
Well, anyway, we had to.
I finally got sick of paying
50 bucks a year for
my monkey license.
- Where do you want
the silverware?
- Well, in the kitchen
where it always goes.
50 bucks!
I'm not gonna pay the
government 50 bucks
for the privilege
of owning a monkey.
How much do you pay for
your little things up there?
- Well, not that much.
- Exactly. So anyway, we're
living in a much better place.
It's quieter, frankly
it's a better neighborhood
and they only charge 10 bucks
a year for the monkey license.
Pretty shrewd, huh?
- It's a nice one
too. Look, it's red.
- Wow. Real neat.
It does seem like kind of a
commotion just to save the $40.
But you know.
- Oh no, Mike, it
only cost 2.3 million
to move the castle,
so it'll pay off
in about 3,512 years, assuming
2% inflation each year.
So you see how much
sense it makes...
- Well, maybe if you'd moved it
with that big deal
brain of yours.
- I'm not that
omnipotent, Pearl.
And besides, we
packed everything up,
moved the castle here
only to unpack it
and put it back again
in the same places.
I mean, why?
- Oh, I actually have a
pretty good reason for that.
It's because.
(Brain Guy groaning)
- Oh, it's real
official too, look.
"For control of parasite and
disease-riddled smelly apes."
That's me. (laughs)
- Go lay down, Bobo, lay down.
As for you up there.
- Oh, I'd imagine that
what with all the moving,
you don't even have time for
a movie for us today, do ya?
Huh, huh, huh?
- Yeah. Right. Oh, no movie.
Oh, except for this one.
And it's a really bad movie.
It's called "Horrors
of Spider Island."
I hope that's okay.
(Bobo barking)
- Real peaceful in the
new neighborhood too.
- Hey, no!
(Bobo barking)
(bots barking)
(alarms blaring)
- Oh no, not the chain
bark, and we got movie sign!
Come on.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors opening)
- [Narrator] Horrors
of Spider Island!
- [Mike] Give us a
chance to sit down.
(sultry music)
- [Crow] It's an anagram
for "Abrabra Navelnite."
- [Tom] Temple Foster, where
they worship Australian beer.
- [Crow] Hey, they're
playing make-out music, Mike.
Whaddya say?
- [Mike] Too bad we can't
grab this movie with a tissue
and crumple it and flush
it down the toilet.
- [Tom] Pacemaker.
Ironically, they used a
lot of microwave ovens
and metal detectors
during this movie.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Spider Island,
home to the stars.
- [Mike] This is
back when every car
was filled with a
private investigator.
- [Tom] Boy, Spider
Island's all built up now.
- [Crow] Hey, that guy
took his boat on land.
(Servo humming along with music)
♪ Parallel parking,
parallel parking ♪
♪ Park park p-p-park. ♪
- [Crow] It's a dames
and broads audition.
- [Mike] Hey, nice office
for an enlisted man.
- Here's Singapore, in
the South of Malaya.
Population,
approximately 550,000.
(indistinct) ship building,
important seaport.
- Doesn't it say anything
about the 32 nightclubs there?
- Have you already
worked down in Singapore?
- Not to work.
However, I once had a
friend an oil sheik.
He took me with him down there.
He was quite a guy.
- Those are the guys that
run around in
turbans, aren't they?
- Listen honey, when they
take those turbans off,
they're just like any other man.
- [Crow] Turban-less.
- Got a light?
- [Tom] Lucky sign.
- Looking forward to
going to Singapore?
- I don't really
care where I dance,
as long as the pay's good.
- [Mike] I'm Bob Box-body.
- That's him there.
- [Tom] I mind very
much if you smoke.
- [Crow] Hey, quit doing your
Sharon Stone impersonation.
- Hi.
- I've already
been to Singapore.
- And you look like it.
- [Mike] (chuckles) And I
said "You look like it."
- Ah!
- [Tom] Dr. Strangelove!
- Hello Gary. Hi Georgia.
You're looking
prettier every day.
How in the world are you doing?
- Mike?
- Yeah?
- Have you told the girls
what this is all about?
- Sure Gary, a tour
for a dancing troop.
First engagement, Singapore.
I have 12 of them
here to pick from.
- [Crow] Enjoy, Gary.
- Okay Georgia.
Let the girls in.
We don't have much time.
- All right if we start
now, Mr. Blackwood?
- Of course.
- Oh, but one at a time please.
- Okay. May.
- [Crow] We're looking for
someone who will sleep with us.
- Smile, would ya?
- How do you do?
- That's Mr.
Webster, the manager.
And this is May, she's
the finest dancer in town.
- [Tom] See?
- What was your last engagement?
- With the Coquettes, one year.
- One of the finest.
- Hmm. Legs?
- Pardon me?
- Mr. Webster would like
to look at your legs.
- Oh, sure.
- [Mike] Suppress
it, suppress it.
- Thank you. You're hired.
Please wait outside.
- Oh, thank you.
- And this is Rhonda Hunter.
- Dancer?
- Not really, but I pick
things up real fast.
- Hmm.
- [Tom] Well, let's
see your clavicle.
- Thank you, we're
looking for dancers,
- But what's that got
to do with Singapore?
- Come on, honey,
don't hold us up.
- [Crow] This is how Ms.
magazine does its hiring.
- Babs?
- [Mike] Babs played
fullback for the Lions.
- This is Babs.
Her legs are worth
their weight in gold.
- Can those golden
legs also dance?
- I was a solo dancer
in the Apollo variety.
- And why did you leave there?
- Oh, the boss
really went for her,
but his wife thought otherwise.
- [Crow] There it is again.
- All right, you
can work with us
as long as you don't
have any affairs.
Mr. Webster doesn't
tolerate any fooling around.
- [Mike] Yeah, that's cool.
- I had all the boys I can take.
- Come on.
Carolyn?
- [Tom] Is this the
Ensure auditions?
- This little one's from
the National Ballet.
- Could you dance a
little bit for us?
- Glad to, would you
put that on for me?
- Sure. Let's have a look.
- [Crow] But none of
that modern stuff,
just shake your dinners.
- [Mike] This is called,
"You'll never have sex with me."
(upbeat piano music)
- [Tom] Thank goodness
she has that belt
or her outfit would
fall right off.
- [Crow] Well boss,
we can always pay her
in cigarettes,
cocaine and coffee.
- [Mike] The Horrors
of Spider Island.
- [Crow] He's supported
by a generous grant
from the Onan foundation
and the Chubb Group.
(upbeat piano music)
- [Tom] Ooh, she made him vomit.
- [Mike] All right,
can the crap, Giselle.
- Thank you, Carolyn.
You dance wonderfully.
- [Mike] For a cow.
- But I'm afraid ballet is
not what we're looking for.
- [Tom] I guess it's
back to my dead-end job
as principal dancer
with the Bolshoi.
- Don't be sad, honey.
I tell you what, come
in again tomorrow.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I've got
something else for you.
- [Crow] Lunch and gossip.
- All right.
- [Mike] It's a dancer
and her seeing eye dancer.
- Here are Gladys and Doreen.
- I told you to let
them in separately.
- These babes have been
working from the start
as a duo number.
- And we would very much like
to stay together if possible.
- On this tour, you'll be
dancing with other girls.
- That doesn't matter.
As long as we get
to go overseas.
- All right, you can
both work with us.
Please send the next one in.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- See you.
- [Tom] The Indigo
Girls of dancing.
- Linda.
- Hello there.
- [Crow] It's Marty Allen.
- Hmm. You're a stripper?
- [Mike] And refinisher, yes.
- [Gary] Didn't I see you work
the Sapphire Club last month?
(bots groaning)
How come you left that place?
- The boss wanted to, I didn't.
- Are you alwaysúso picayunish?
- [Mike] No, I'm Lithuanian.
- That depends on
the boss, boss.
Shall I dance for you?
- [Crow] Yes, for
God's sake, yes!
- That's not necessary.
You're hired. Wait outside.
- Okay.
- [Mike] It's a nice day, I'm
going to go home like this.
- Next girl, please.
- [Tom] Strip, come on!
- My name is Nelly Hickson.
- A new one, I haven't
seen her work yet
but she's always been
with good troops.
- Let's see her dance.
- [Mike] Great, that's
good. You're hired.
(jazzy music)
- [Tom] Pat Nixon gets
down at the White House.
- [Mike] She studied
under Rose Marie.
- [Crow] I think her
timing belt is too tight.
- [Tom] Look out, Singapore.
- [Mike] Brought to you by
the National Garter Council.
- [Crow] It's the drunk
aunt at the wedding dance.
- [Tom] And so it just
goes on like that.
- You're hired.
Please wait outside.
(instrumental theme music)
Mr. Blackwood has supplied
all the girls we need.
- That's fine, Georgia.
Go and tell the girls
when costume and dance
rehearsals will start,
will you please?
- [Georgia] All right.
- [Mike] Like my
transition lenses?
- Listen Gary, I thought
you were the boss,
but you Georgia
select all the girls.
- I select all the girls.
- You? But you
didn't say a word.
- Why should I?
I have a little trick.
When I keep my
legs apart like so,
it means I'm not interested.
When I cross them like
this, ah, then it's okay.
(laughing)
- You're a crazy guy.
When do things get underway?
- [Tom] I'm having my
body reblocked tomorrow.
- Oh, 10 days.
- 10 days? Well then,
have a good trip.
- Thank you.
- [Crow] Hundreds of
dancers are loaded
into a C-31 transport
and dropped on Singapore.
(engines roaring)
- [Mike] I never get to
fly with exotic dancers,
I get the seed
salesmen from Lacrosse.
(engines roaring)
- [Crow] Singapore's right
across the Hudson River.
- [Tom] from Los
Angeles, they take off
from New York to
go to Singapore.
(engines rumbling)
- [Mike] Okay, there.
I've looked at clouds
from both sides now.
And frankly, I'm
not that impressed.
- [Crow] Hmm, this
is a good storm,
but it's not the perfect storm.
- [Tom] Oh, they had to divert
around Charlie Rich's hair.
- We're now flying over the
Pacific Ocean near Honolulu.
Altitude is 15,000 feet.
- [Crow] Wait, 1,500.
Oh crap, does anyone know
how to read these things?
- [Pilot] Mayday,
mayday, mayday.
Clipper 247, Clipper 247.
- [Tom] Mayday...
Hey, slow down!
- [Pilot] Attempting
emergency landing.
- [Mike] I think
they'll pull out of it.
- Repeat your position.
Repeat your position.
- [Tom] I'm sitting.
- Damn, I can't pick
them up anymore.
Clipper 247!
- [Crow] So is the
beverage service over?
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Our Clinique!
- [Tom] Ow.
- [Crow] Oh, Abby's running
more how we met stories.
- No Mr. Hastings.
I can only repeat.
There's absolutely no reason
yet to fear the worst.
Until now, we only know
that the plane caught fire
and that we've
lost radio contact.
- [Mike] Well,
there's absolutely
nothing to be worried about.
- Yeah, I'll let
you know immediately
as soon as I hear something new.
- [Tom] Finally, I
can read Savage Love.
- [Crow] Aah, I spent a
brief second without alcohol!
- [Mike] Don't waste
time with the cap, drink!
Now smoke, now drink.
Now answer the phone!
- Blackwood Agency.
No, Mr. Alberts, I don't
have any further information.
But of course there's a
search party out there.
I tell you, their a few have
been looking all over for them.
There's still hope,
even after four days.
Yes, I'll call you as soon
as I hear something new.
- [Mike] Let's see, I was
thinking of doing something.
Ah, there.
♪ Sun is rising ♪
(water burbling)
- [Tom] That didn't work
out, so back to this shot.
- [Mike] Wow, I almost thought
we were in trouble there,
flaming out and
crashing at high speed
into the ocean and all.
(woman crying)
- [Tom] We've been in
the water for an hour.
Would you stop
chewing on my foot?
- [Crow] Survival meals
are so high in fat.
- Stop that bawling.
You're driving us all nuts.
- [Tom] Debbie goes
immediately into vacation mode.
(woman sobbing)
- [Mike] Oh, when did
they pick up K.D. Lang?
- Water, just one swallow.
- No more today.
Tomorrow you'll
get another ration.
- [Crow] Of me.
- Gary, give her some water.
- What do you think you are?
- [Tom] I'm trying
to tan my shins.
- The fifth night, we
can't hold out much longer.
- You're starting
that too, Georgia?
- [Mike] That
darkens my features.
- A ship has to
by here sometime.
Why, we've got to at
least see some land.
- [Crow] How big can
the ocean be, anyway?
- [Tom] Oh, if only they could
find a desalinization plant.
- Water, please give me water.
- [Mike] I need to
rinse out a few things.
- Look, a bird!
- [Gary] Where there are
birds, there must be land.
Are you crazy? Give that to me.
- [Crow] That's my Hai Karate.
- [Tom] They're already
planning a Playboy
"Girls of the
Plane Crash" issue.
- Look there, Gary, over there!
- [Mike] Ovah
way-ah? Oh, they-ah.
- [Gary] Land, that was land.
Help me paddle.
We've got to make it.
Paddle with your hands.
- [Crow] Or your panties or
your breasts or whatever.
(water splashing)
- [Mike] If there's land,
there's gotta be a day spa.
- Don't stop now.
We'll make it.
Not far now.
(women talking over each other)
- [Crow] I see a tall Spaniard
in a white suit with a midget.
- [Mike] Wait, I forgot
my purse on the plane.
- [Crow] I hope the
natives like fan dancing.
- [Tom] Let me get, ow,
ow, sharp coral, ow.
- [Crow] Ow, ow, pufferfish.
Owie owie owie ow.
- [Mike] Bullhead, ooh.
- Oh, I can't go on.
- Come on, I'll help you.
- [Tom] Just go the five
feet to shore without me.
- [Mike] Let's pretend
we're evolving.
- [Crow] An Exxon girl
tanker ran aground.
- There you are, Georgia.
- [Tom] Just north of Florida.
- Lie down.
- I can't go...
- [Mike] I can't wait to
get these pantyhose off.
- [Crow] They must've filmed
this during an eclipse.
- [Tom] The catch of the day.
(Mike imitates crying)
- [Crow] They should just start
putting handles on
women for easy carrying.
- [Tom] He fish are averting
their eyes right now.
- [Mike] We got totally
drunk on the rocks.
- [Crow] So they
sat around floating
for a while and now
they're exhausted.
- [Tom] The woman is a
cold-blooded creature,
and must lay on
rocks to warm up.
- [Mike] Camera
lenses were crafted
from carbon rods back then.
- [Tom] (grunting) You gotta get
back on the Figurines, honey.
- [Mike] Ow, my neck.
- [Crow] I gotta go back
and get Camryn Manheim,
it may take awhile.
- [Mike] No, I don't
want to be put by Debbie.
- [Tom] I'm going to fashion
you all into a crude hut.
- [Mike] He's kind of
an early Carmine Ragusa.
- Georgia, darling.
- [Crow] Make me
some coffee and oh,
get the Coast Guard on the line.
- [Tom] I can't
believe Northwest
only offered us mini pretzels.
- Oh, Gary.
- [Mike] There there. Take
comfort in my beefiness.
- [Crow] It's a giant
sea donut, we're saved!
Oh, it's the raft.
(Servo humming)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
(grunting)
- Mike, what the
hell are you doing?
- Trying to extricate
myself from this giant web.
- Well be careful will ya,
and don't disturb the giant fly.
That's our lunch.
- Okay, you know, I'm
not going to go into
how you made a giant web,
I just want to know why?
- Well, I think the more
important question is
what possessed you to leap
blindly across the bridge
and get caught in
the first place?
Do you routinely spring out
of the theater like a gazelle?
- Crow, how do I get outta here?
- Good question.
Can you excrete oily web-proof
spittle from your mouth?
- Uh, yeah. I think so.
Hang on, let me get a quick-
Of course I can't.
- Hey, hey.
I'm not the one who
sprinted headlong
into a large and
very obvious web.
- Here's some roasted
potato bug and dip.
This web's going to have
us eatin' like kings.
Mike, what the
hell are you doing?
- Apparently he
was pogo sticking
blindfolded across the bridge.
- too bad. Let's eat.
I had no idea there were so many
giant insects on the satellite.
- I had no idea they'd
be so delicious.
- Hey, hey.
Now there's a giant
spider, help me.
- That's a pretty
lame impression
of David Hedison
in "The Fly," Mike.
- Come on Crow, the
giant mantis fingers
are bubbling hot with cheese.
- Yummy! See ya, Mike.
- Well, I'm dead and
we'll be right back.
Hey!
(instrumental theme music)
(sultry saxophone music)
- [Mike] Corn's
looking good here.
(Tom hums along with music)
- [Crow] And
Hedonism II is born.
- [Tom] I've
enslaved the natives.
- Water!
- [Crow] That's what
dried soup mix needs.
- [Mike] Ah, the girls
deserve to see my thickness.
- [Crow] Do we
have to watch this?
- Water, water, water, water!
Come on, come on, come on.
(women exclaiming)
- Fresh drinking water.
- [Tom] The best way to get
it is to lick it off my chest.
- Spring water.
- [Mike] The graceful,
nimble dancers.
(women exclaiming)
- [Crow] I am one lucky bastard.
- [Tom] Oh, I hope this
water isn't fattening.
- Oh, is there anything
more wonderful than water?
- Okay, girls. That's enough.
Let's go and have a look around.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ready? Let's go.
- [Mike] But I'm severely
dehydrated, can I drink more?
- [Crow] No, we must get moving.
- Feeling better now?
Don't lag behind.
- [Mike] Let's go visit
Brooke Shields and
Christopher Atkins.
- Heels are too high for here.
- Hey, here's your scarf.
- Oh, keep it.
- Coming?
- [Tom] What, he's not going
to carry us this time? (scoffs)
- [Mike] Um, schlemiel
schlimazel, anyone?
- Ow
- [Crow] My tender man skin.
- Careful, girls.
- [Tom] Don't let my raw
sexuality overwhelm you.
(all imitate women mumbling)
- What a strange sight.
- Well, let's keep going.
- [Mike] I refuse to
comment on what you said.
- [Crow] Hot, muddy
foreign chick action.
- Ouch, my shoe.
- [Mike] "Feels like
a sneaker," my ass.
- Gary, look what I just found.
- [Tom] A stick!
- A hammer. There must be
someone on this island.
A hammer with a long handle.
- [Crow] That's me.
- It must be for the purpose
of excavating some
sort of metal.
Most probably uranium.
- Can you eat that?
- Yeah, you can try it.
Come on. Let's go and find out.
- [Mike] Be sure and murmur
and coo some more too.
Uh-huh, good.
Yeah. Keep it up now.
That's it. Hey Susie,
I don't hear you.
(women murmuring)
- [Crow] And people
complain that there
aren't any strong
roles for women.
- Come on, hurry up.
Look, come here.
- [Mike] Duck, swim.
- Look, a cabin!
- [Tom] The
Leatherface residence.
(women murmuring happily)
- [Crow] I call
the bathroom first!
- [Mike] No, me.
- I get it.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Charlotte's
killing spree.
- Oooh...
- [Crow] It's gorgeous.
- Let's get outta here.
- [Mike] All right, now watch
how a man screams in horror.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] He was caught in the
middle of a cheerleading move.
- A dead man, in a huge web.
- [Mike] Oh, I was
looking at the wallpaper.
- [Crow] Murmur, murmur,
slightly more intense murmur.
- [Tom] We've got
spirit, yes we do.
We've got spirit,
how 'bout... (groans)
- [Crow] MRxL.
Get rid of the dead guy,
turn on the LP tanks,
put out the dog,
we're ready to go.
- [Mike] Can I be
in your cluster?
- Hey there!
Come on.
- [Crow] She was appointed
acting Gary in his absence.
- [Tom] Damn, I was just
about to pinch her tush.
- The poor professor.
When he made the last
entry in the diary,
he didn't know how
horribly he would die.
- Well, the discovery
of the uranium deposits
didn't help him
any, even if it does
represent a tremendous fortune.
- [Crow] Well, gotta
tighten my shirt.
- We must keep it from the girls
that Professor Green had
a premonition of his fate.
- You see here in
the last paragraph,
he says he thought something
terrible was going to happen.
He just felt the danger.
- I wonder where that
peculiar hissing came from
that he always heard.
- [Tom] The audience.
- Oh Gary, I'm terribly scared.
I'm so afraid.
- Don't worry, Georgia.
- Oh, okay. I won't, thanks.
- As long as I'm around,
nothing will happen to you.
I promise.
- [Crow] Look into my nose now.
- Hi, Georgia.
- I'm hungry.
- I've made something
for you to eat.
Luckily, there were
some canned goods here.
- [Tom] Wardrobe, we have
a birth scene problem.
- It must have been a
really gigantic spider
to be able to spin
such a huge web.
Maybe there are more of them.
- But a bite like that couldn't
have come from a spider.
- Aren't you at all afraid?
- Afraid? I can't
change anything.
- I'm terribly afraid something
awful is going to happen.
- [Mike] Unlike the plane crash.
- (gasps) Look!
- [Tom] It's our
friend who just left.
- We found the professor's
trunk full of stuff.
They'll certainly be useful.
- [Crow] Boxer
shorts and his truss.
- One, four, five, six,
seven, eight. Okay.
- [Tom] We can sell this
stuff to the others.
- If we divide the
provisions up carefully,
they should last for a month.
- What did you say
Georgia, a month?
Do you really think I'll
be here a whole month?
- I don't know.
- [Crow] Thank you, Georgia.
- We have to go tomorrow
to the highest cliff
and light a smoke signal to
try and attract the ship.
10, 11, 12.
- [Mike] Hey, they brought
Virginia Graham along.
- Give me that shirt!
- No, it belongs to me.
After all, I found it.
- But my dress is in
worse shape than yours.
- No, I want to have it.
Give it to me.
(women yelling)
- Stop that fighting.
Give me that shirt.
- [Crow] You both get no shirts.
- Georgia.
- [Tom] Cook this for dinner.
- Thanks, Gary.
- I suppose we
could have guessed
that Georgia would
be getting it.
- [Crow] That sheer fabric
would make a good shirt.
- Haven't you ever noticed
that Gary pampers her?
- What's this?
Where did you get the pullover?
- I found it here, if you
don't have anything against it.
- Now stop it or I'll
take care of both of you.
Give me something to drink.
- [Tom] Rice vinegar's
fine, thanks.
- Take it easy, Gary.
We're all a little nervous.
It's really no wonder.
- Don't you think I'd rather
be in a bar in Singapore
with a nice cold
drink, than to be on
this godforsaken place?
- [Mike] With eight hot babes?
- Drinking this horrible stuff?
- [Tom] How-er-able?
(instrumental theme music)
- Darn heat.
(cup clattering)
- [Crow] It didn't
stay in the air.
- Cut it out, will ya?
And stop making so much noise.
- If you don't like it,
you can do the dishes.
Or do you think I'm doing
this for my own pleasure?
- Stop blowing your top
and dry up, will ya?
- [Mike] I can't wait
til the spiders eat you.
- (sighing) I simply can't stand
this frightful heat any longer.
- [Tom] Ah, the movie
reveals its true purpose.
- How about throwing your
dirty blouse someplace else?
I want sleep
- [Crow] Excuse me, Charro?
- [Mike] Hey, I have some
Slim Fast bars, we're saved.
- [Tom] So anyone
wanna catfight or?
- I sure hope you don't
lose your lipstick.
You'd hardly be able to get
along on this Island without it.
- [Crow] Her accent changed
three times in one sentence.
(knocking)
- It's about time.
Now I'll shower.
Give it here.
- Come on, come on, girls.
Let's go to sleep.
- I'm going to sleep outside.
- Me too.
- Goodnight.
- Goodnight, Kate.
- [Tom] Tomorrow
I'm going to try
to pull my pants up to my chest.
♪ Taking off clothes music ♪
- [Mike] Reporting for bed, sir!
- [Tom] I'm getting
mixed signals from her.
- [Crow] Try crossing
your legs now, pal.
- [Mike] You know, guys who play
the muted trumpet
love these movies.
It's the only time
they get work.
- [Tom] Ma'am? Hey,
lady, over here!
Turn around, come on.
- [Crow] He has Torgo area.
- Ugh
- I found the
professor's revolver.
- Get some sleep, Gary.
- I can't. I think I'll
go out for a little walk.
But don't worry, I'll
be back very shortly.
- [Mike] This condescending pat
will hold you til I get back.
- [Tom] Ooh, I am
so nude under this.
- [Crow] Man, this is too
much even for me, Mike.
Can we see a couple
of elderly scientists
in lab coats talking nonstop?
- [Tom] I'm feeling so, I don't
know, erotic or something.
- [Mike] Hey, this is not
the Amelia Earhart story.
Who are they kidding?
- [Crow] Ooh, I'm
glad I added a porch.
- [Mike] With my luck,
I'd crash with ZZ Top.
- [Tom] (chuckling)
I'm impotent.
- [Crow] Um, you're
in my writhing space.
- Gary.
- [Mike] Wow, can you really
do that through pants?
- Oh, Gary.
- [Crow] Pull your
slacks up higher.
- [Tom] oh, I'd love to
braid your back hair.
- [Mike] Whoa, their faces
have actually melded.
- Gary!
- [Crow] Your infidelity
mildly irritates me.
- Damned heat.
I don't know what
I'm doing anymore.
- [Tom] Yes, I've
been unfaithful,
but it was like 87 degrees.
- [Mike] Okay, come here.
Hey, hold still will ya?
Hang on. There.
- [Crow] It's also kind
of windy, that too.
And high humidity.
(thunder crashing)
- [Tom] Good
chest-rubbing weather
- [Mike] Oh, slipped in
that spider flop there.
- [Crow] I've been
lifting, whaddya think?
(thunder crashing)
- [Tom] So this is a sexy,
spider-filled version
of "The Tempest."
- [Mike] Hey, come
into my parlor.
- [Tom] You see if it
was in the low seventies,
I would never have jammed
my tongue down her throat.
- [Crow] I fell out of the tree!
- [Tom] Gary, thy
Lord commandeth,
tug your pants down a
titch and put on a shirt.
- [Mike] Since when do spiders
need to expend so
much effort to climb?
- [Crow] Hey, a nice
big one down there.
- [Mike] Spider pile!
- [Tom] Oh, you want a hickey,
I'll give you a damn hickey.
- [Mike] Red Lobster snow
crabs finally fight back
- [Tom] Get off me, you
exoskeletal piece of-
(gun firing)
- Girls, wake up! I
heard them clearly.
- Oh, I hope nothing's
happened to Gary.
- [Crow] I hope my coating
of oil will protect me.
- [Mike] (coughing)
Too many malts...
- [Crow] Damn, just when
girls began to like me.
- [Tom] Hairy palms,
Mother was right!
(growling)
- I'm going. If you're not
going with me, I'm going alone.
- Stay here, don't
leave us alone!
(screaming)
- [Mike] My little brother's
messing with our tent.
- [Tom] And so our story ends.
D'oh!
- Oh, just leave
everything as it is.
We must find Gary.
Babs and Ann, you go
in that direction.
- Where in the world is Kate?
- Here, Georgia.
- You two go in that direction.
Kate and May will
go along with me.
- [Tom] Wait, who told
them to get dressed?
(women murmuring)
- What about me?
- You, you remain here
and put things in
order while we're gone.
- Huh.
- [Mike] Start by
alphabetizing our shoes.
- [Crow] The endangered
wild Daryl Hannah.
- Hey, Gary!
- [Tom] I know you're out here.
I can smell your Brylcream.
- Would you quit that whistling,
you're making me nervous.
- I'm not afraid when I whistle.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Don't buy
extra strength Biore.
[Tom] The king approacheth.
- Gary!
- [Mike] How about
a dish of oil?
- Gary!
- Come on, we gotta keep moving.
- Not me, I'm
staying right here.
- [Crow] I've got feet
like Billy Pilgrim.
- Did you hear anything?
- No.
- But there's
something moving there.
- I don't hear anything.
- [Tom] They're all
dubbed by the same person.
- Gary!
- Hey Gladys, don't
leave me alone.
- Then hurry up.
Gary!
- Gary!
♪ Gary, Gary ♪
- [Mike] I like that.
- Gary!
- [Crow] I'm Gary. Look for me.
- [Tom] Who's going to tell us
when to eat and
when to go to bed?
- Gary!
- [Mike] I won't go out with
a half-man
half-spider, I'm sorry.
- [Crow] Okay
honey, you're alone.
You can ease up on the sex now.
- [Tom] Feast your eyes
on my good stuff, nature.
- [Mike] Well hello, shrubbery.
- [Crow] I wasn't
even being sexy
til the dirty sax music started.
- [Tom] Her skirt is
more slip than skirt.
- [Crow] She's a sexy
Henry David Thoreau.
- [Mike] I can make these
into primitive pasties.
- [Crow] Strange that she's
a published medical ethicist.
- [Tom] Do I turn
you on too, brook?
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] There's a
touchdown behind her.
(screaming)
- I heard a scream.
I heard it plainly.
The scream came from there.
- [Crow] Should we say "Gary?"
- [Tom] Broke a heal.
- [Mike] me too.
- Me too.
- [Mike] They'll
cover the coffin
with flags slit real high.
- [Crow] Not real, not at all.
- How awful.
- [Mike] You know,
Susan, before she died,
she told me she
thought you were fat.
- She's been strangled.
- The spider.
(instrumental theme music)
- Georgia, who's next?
- That would be a
Miss Pearl Forrester.
- Forrester, hey? (chuckling)
- Oh, you're going
to like her, Gary.
She's great.
- Whee.
(Bobo giggling)
Huzzah.
Pearl, something's happening.
- What's up, cotton ball?
- What's up?
I'm taking some
dancers to Singapore.
You do well there,
the sky's the limit.
- Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
Singapore, and then
off-off-Broadway,
then off-Broadway
and then Broadway!
- Oh good luck, you guys!
- You too!
Good luck, Bobo!
- Luck, hell. This is
for a shot at fame.
Right now I couldn't
hate you more.
Spread out, you two!
(ragtime music)
- Next.
- Son of a-
- Beat it, has-been.
(80s-style synth music)
- (muttering) Good, not bad.
- Okay baby, you're in.
- Yes! (laughing)
Eat it, loser.
- No.
(soft piano music)
- (muttering) Gary likes that.
- That's great, sister.
Now give us a little leg.
- Leg? Oh sure.
Brain Guy?
- Oh, yup.
(screaming)
(alarms blaring)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors opening)
- Ann, Ann!
- Oh it's horrible.
Oh Georgia, the
professor's been killed,
Gary's disappeared and now
we've just buried Linda.
Which one of us is
going to be next?
I don't want to die,
I don't want to die!
- Ann, Ann! Stop it, will you?
Stop it, before you
drive us all crazy.
- Not me, not me.
- And I tell you they'll
never find us, never.
- But I'm sure the
police are moving
heaven and hell
to find us, honey.
- [Crow] You'll be fine, ladies.
- The police?
The cops I know,
if they catch you
speeding a little bit
or find you drunk,
they send you right
off to the cooler.
But you just let
somebody get lost,
and they won't lift a finger.
Do you believe that they'll go
running around for a
few broads who are lost?
- But how are they to know
that we've been rescued
and on this little Island?
- Rescued, who's been rescued?
We perhaps?
Show me the island, show me.
Where does it lie in the
ocean? show it to me.
- By the time they find
us, we'll all be dead.
You, you and you,
one after the other.
- Babs!
- [Mike] Bang?
- Get ahold of
yourself, you're only
getting all the girls worked up.
- [Tom] Great.
- Well, if it
isn't Miss Georgia.
Of all people, it has to be you.
Who has Gary and Linda
on her conscience, who?
- [Mike] I'll be
right there, hang on.
- Babs, do you know
what you're saying?
- Exactly. Through
your jealousy.
You should never have left
Linda alone in the cabin.
- Shut up, will you?
What can Georgia do
about Linda's death?
- Take your hands off me,
or I'll break your arm.
- Just you try that
baby, take this!
- [Tom] Oh man, I don't think
I can take another girl fight.
- [Crow] So there
will be whipping.
Okay, I can roll with that.
(slapping)
- [Mike] Carmelite
nuns, the real story.
- [Tom] (whimpering)
Underpants! Oh...
(women yelling)
- [Mike] Ah, Servo. He fainted.
- [Tom] Sorry, Mike. It's
a little much for me.
- [Mike] Easy, steady.
- [Crow] The Lennon Sisters
were fighting more and more.
- [Mike] Man, they're future
governors of Minnesota.
- [Crow] I usually have
to go to a website to see
this kind of thing, like
nakedwrestlinggiantesses.com.
(women yelling)
- [Mike] Daisy Mae is upset.
(women screaming)
- [Tom] Backstage
at Lilith Fair,
Joan Osborne and Jewel
have another brawl.
- [Crow] Ooh, you
have nice skin.
Start with a little foundation.
(screaming)
Okay. I'm trying to help.
(Mike humming
Beethoven's 5th Symphony)
- [Tom] Where should we
spill this oil, captain?
- Come, come!
- Is the ship
getting any closer?
- I don't know.
Come on, throw it off.
- [Tom] I don't know.
- Should I get some more?
- No, no, that's enough.
That's giving enough smoke.
- [Crow] Kathy Lee Gifford
tried to rescue them,
but they turned her down.
- They must see us! They
can't just leave us here.
Hello, hello!
- Stop all that screaming,
you're driving me crazy.
- Let me go!
Hello, take us with you.
- [Mike] Damn Californian,
it never helps anyone.
- We're over here.
Please don't forget us!
Yell with me. They must hear us.
Hello, hello there!
Take us with you.
May, it's sailed right by.
It's sailed by.
- [Tom] Even though we said,
"Hello, take us with you!"
- We'll never get home now.
Never again.
- 28 days. 28 long
days and nights.
- [Mike] That's how
late my videos are.
- And nobody even
knows we're here.
- And today a ship
sailed right by us.
Our rescue so close.
- Ann, May.
- [Crow] Turns out
we're on Catalina.
- Oh Georgia, a ship.
There, a ship.
- Oh, it's gone. How terrible.
And we only have enough
food left for three days.
- [Mike] We'll have to
eat the Hormel stuff.
- Ann, Ann!
Come on back, come on.
- [Tom] They're missing a
huge nutritious salt lick
right under their feet.
- [Crow] So they founded
the Isle of Lesbos.
- [Mike] You know, with
no men there, they'll stop
shaving their legs and
armpits and their upper lips.
Basically they'll
start looking like men.
- [Bob] You go ahead
and start unloading.
I'll take the oars up.
- Okay Bob.
- [Tom] Would you please
get out of the boat?
- What are you carrying
the oars so far away for?
Afraid the mermaids
will steal our boat?
- Don't talk to me about women
on this godforsaken island.
- [Mike] You're my belly warmer.
- Should have taken one along
as part of your rations.
- I wanted to, but
it wasn't approved.
- Tuh.
- [Crow] here's
no need for "tuh."
- Hey, come on over here
and give me a hand, will ya?
- Okay, I'm coming.
- Take it easy.
Easy, now. Easy.
Boy, that junk is heavy.
- [Mike] Man, how many
heads did you put in this?
- Bob, you know, I'm sort
of glad the professor
picked us out to help
him with his work.
Even though it's
lonely over here.
- [Tom] Good backstory, right?
- Give me some whiskey.
There aren't any chicks,
but at least some whiskey.
- You only think about
whiskey and women.
- [Mike] And drugs.
- You better change or
you'll never get any place.
- Get off my back, I'm
sick of your preaching.
- Take the professor
for example.
That guy's always been lucky.
- While we explore all sorts
of islands for six months,
he comes with us once
and finds good stuff.
And of all places on
this miserable island.
- Stop grumbling, will ya?
- Ah, go on.
- [Crow] I'll say "tuh" again.
- I'll go look for
the profession now.
- Okay. Get on outta
here, will you?
In the meantime I'll unload.
- And have fun.
- Yeah, sure.
- [Mike] Remember, we
work for the professor
and we've been gone six months.
- [Tom] Hey, they have a
Swiss Colony booze basket.
- [Crow] Now to balance
my electrolytes,
- [Tom] Drink it and
hear girls giggle.
- [Mike] Ah-
Oh damn, there's
a tree in my way.
- [Crow] You can hear footsteps.
Does the tree have
wood flooring?
- [Tom] I'll impress the ladies
by impersonating a sloth.
(water splashing)
- [Mike] This poor guy
thinks they're manatees.
(playful music)
- [Crow] We're nude
and have no nipples
and we're uniformly colored.
- [Tom] (giggles)
I'm in the deep end.
(playful music)
♪ It's kooky and
we're swimming ♪
♪ And we're nude and
we are swimming ♪
♪ And we're kooky and
we have no nipples ♪
(playful music)
- [Crow] Mmm, girl drops.
- [Tom] Ah yes, the hustle
and bustle of city life.
(Mike imitating traffic noise)
- [Crow] Taxi!
- [Tom] That's right,
wedge into the crevasse.
- [Crow] Man, the best
thing I ever found
in a tide pool was a sea urchin.
- [Tom] There's a giant woman
swimming off the
cliffs of Dover!
(screaming)
- [Mike] The sea
spider's attacking!
(screaming)
- Gladys! Gladys!
Quick, girls, we're in danger.
Make for the beach.
- We can't leave her here.
- But all of us will be killed.
Let's go. Come on.
- [Crow] Ow, I scraped
my stomach on the rocks.
- [Tom] Wow. Whole
Island full of Gingers.
- Look over there!
(gasps)
- [Mike] Okay, what? Yes?
What are we looking at?
- [Tom] Meanwhile,
Singapore suffers
through a severe
dancer shortage.
- [Crow] The Dixie Chicks
go big game hunting.
- How terrible.
- The web?
(indistinct)
- The gun!
- [Mike] Wayne LaPierre
is on the island.
- Gary took it with
him that night.
- [Tom] It'll make
a neat accessory.
- [Mike] Um, I'm only sleeping,
I see you stealing that.
- And this is his bracelet.
- [Tom] Most of the candy
hasn't been eaten off yet.
- But where is Gary?
- Please Georgia, let's
go. I'm so afraid.
- Perhaps there are
more spiders around.
- [Crow] At least I got a
kicky scarf out of this deal.
Hey!
- Come on, sit with me.
- What to you want from me?
- Well, I'll give
you three guesses
- [Mike] I don't know,
I'm pretty pissed
about you attacking me.
- I was going to ask
you for the time.
- [Tom] I'm laying
on a dead man-of-war.
- [Mike] Well, Burt
Lancaster he's not.
- [Crow] He's not
even Bert Lahr.
- Georgia, Georgia!
- Here we are.
- Gladys is gone
down by the lagoon.
We were swimming when suddenly
she was pulled into the reeds.
- And she screamed terribly.
- Who was it, did
you see anyone?
- No. it all
happened so quickly.
- A scream.
- And she'd already disappeared.
- Maybe the spider killed
the professor and Linda.
We found a gigantic
spider, dead.
It was shot with the
professor's own revolver.
- And Gary's bracelet was
laying there beside it.
(Tom singing "Le Marseillaise")
- Hands up! Stop or I'll shoot.
- [Mike] Give us
all your Pamprin.
- Hey, hello baby.
- Hands up!
- Anything you wish.
- Keep going into the cabin.
- What a coincidence,
that's where I wanted to go.
- I said get going!
- [Crow] I'll have
Babs mess you up.
- All righty.
- I think he's handsome.
- He doesn't look so terrible.
- They're the really
dangerous ones.
- Too bad.
- [Tom] That woman
sounds like Urkel.
- [Mike] I just escaped
from Beau Geste.
- Okay, turn around.
Where's Gladys?
- [Crow] Spying
on the Stevenses.
- What did you do with her?
- Let me speak to him.
Where is Gladys?
- Gladys? No idea.
I don't know the young
lady, unfortunately.
We just got here,
down at the lagoon.
- You see, Georgia?
Where we were swimming.
And that's where
Gladys disappeared.
- On the lagoon?
Ah.
- [Tom] Will you terrorize
me again tomorrow?
(laughing)
- Don't laugh.
You'll be sorry about that.
- Oh, I don't know.
Just look at what's
coming down the path.
- [Mike] Mr. McFeely?
- Gladys!
- [Crow] He attacked me
and now we're engaged!
(women talking excitedly)
- My friend Bob.
We work together
for Professor Green.
- He's a big uranium
research man.
I met him before in the reeds.
- A researching researcher.
- Then you had
better luck than I.
I was nearly shot by that.
That is, if the revolver
had been loaded.
- [Mike] Yeah, uh-huh.
- And you? You here
on a summer vacation?
- Hmm, fine summer vacation.
If we hadn't found this island,
we wouldn't be here
to tell the story.
We crashed on our
way to Singapore.
- Ah, then you're the American
dance troop that got lost.
- Yes. How do you know that?
- All the newspapers in the
world have carried your story.
- I bet Professor
Green was surprised
when all these girls showed up.
- Professor Green is dead.
- [Crow] Well-said.
- What's with the
professor? Dead, what?
- He was hanging in
a huge spiderweb.
That's how we found him.
Linda is dead and Gary, our
manager, has also disappeared.
- A spiderweb?
Do you really believe that?
- By the way, our ship is
coming back in two days.
We must radio information
right away so that
they can send an agent
to clear the matter up.
- You mean it, a
ship's coming by?
- Our expedition ship.
- And it will take us with it?
- Yeah, of course.
(women exclaiming)
- [Tom] Not so fast, Gladys.
I'd like to sample the others.
- [Mike] Wow, she
should depilate.
- Isn't it pretty?
The boys will be
surprised when they see
how we dress ourselves up
in our island costumes.
- [Crow] Boys? Is there
a Cub Scout troop?
- And they promised
us real whiskey, kid.
I can hardly wait. Hold this.
- Shall I put this in my hair?
- You look great. Just
like a real islander.
- Well I am, haven't I
been here for four weeks?
- I can't believe
it, we'll be back
in New York in a couple of days.
- When we tell them at home
what has happened to us,
nobody's going to believe us.
- Where are Georgia and Ann?
- Outside on the veranda.
(Tom groans)
- [Crow] Mike,
Servo's down again.
- [Mike] Oh. Hey, Tom.
Wake up.
- [Tom] Sorry, Mike. Flesh...
- What's important for
me is that Jimmy's there.
- Who is Jimmy?
- My friend, we're
going to be married.
- [Crow] Even though
he's invisible.
- What if he's got
eyes for another?
- You don't believe
that yourself.
I'd scratch his eyes
out and he knows it.
- Kids, we made radio
contact with the ship
and we'll be picked up tomorrow!
And tonight we'll dance
and really raise the roof.
- [Mike] Wow, these
Amish barn raisings
get wilder all the time.
- [Tom] I'm gonna
call the rescue boat,
tell 'em to take their time.
- [Mike] Next dance
is with me, Ron.
- [Tom] She dances as
well as Bruce Springsteen.
♪ This gun's for hire ♪
- [Tom] Okay now,
suck in the gut.
- [Mike] Unfortunately,
she took lessons
at the Arthur
Miller dance studio.
- [Tom] I think I broke
a rib tightening my belt.
- Tell me, what kind
of a girl is Ann?
- Unusually quiet,
and one of the nicest.
She's away from her
for the first time.
Her folks live in Minnesota.
- [Crow] Their governor's
a huge bald Nazi.
- I've never seen
her so relaxed.
- [Mike] Or puffy.
- I'd like to dance with her.
[Crow] but my crotch
stuffing restricts me.
- [Tom] Hi, been looking for
a bloated man with a scarf?
- [Mike] So, Minnesota. That
must be passive-aggressive.
You know, anthropologists
would call this a mating dance.
What do you say?
- [Crow] So, you into scouting?
- [Tom] Twirling?
He must be mad!
- [Crow] Mike, could you
inject me into this film?
- [Tom] I'm worried that Eric
Von Zipper's gonna show up.
- [Mike] This is how
I view the world.
Everyone else is out doing this,
while I sit in my underwear
eating a toasted cheese sandwich
and drinking a nice beer.
- [Crow] Yeah, true.
- Come on Bobby, I want
to be all alone with you.
- How 'bout the house?
- Not in the house. Someplace
where we'll be all alone.
- You know what?
We'll meet at the lagoon.
- Okay, but so that
no one will notice.
- We'll meet in 15 minutes on
the trail down to the water.
All set?
- Of course.
- But be on time.
I hate waiting.
- [Tom] Why couldn't
this be on every channel,
like the State of
the Union Address?
- Thanks.
- [Crow] Hmm, women or
booze, women or booze?
Hey, women and booze!
(whistling)
- Having a good time
with the chicks?
- [Mike] Nah, mine's
from Minnesota.
- Shut your mouth.
- Falling for her?
- Hmm.
(Tom imitates liquid guzzling)
- [Crow] Minnesota, huh?
Boy that Harold Stassen is
a bright young face, huh?
- [Mike] I drooled in
it, I hope that's okay.
- Thank you.
- [Tom] I didn't think you'd
drink that much. Oh well.
- Tell me, are you
always so quiet?
- When you've lived on
islands for a long time,
you forget how to say
nice things to girls.
- Well try it once.
- [Crow] Uh, do you like bugs?
- Well, I'm really glad
that your airplane crashed.
- Well, that's a
nice thing to say.
- I mean-
- [Mike] I'm glad
your puppy died.
- I mean, otherwise I wouldn't
have gotten to know you.
And I'm glad about that.
- Oh, you say that to everybody.
- No, Ann.
I don't know any
girls, and when I think
of the ones I do,
I'd rather work.
- Well, I must say
you certainly are
a master at paying compliments.
- Perhaps you're,
perhaps you're right.
I should pay more
attention to young women.
- [Tom] Maybe I
wouldn't be so gay.
- Sometimes I envy Bob.
He's so uninhibited
and carefree.
- Bobby? Any girl is
good enough for him.
(instrumental theme music)
A real man is interested
in only one girl.
- And I'm a, well
I'm a real man.
- How?
- [Mike] Ow.
- Because I'm really
interested only in one girl.
- Who's that? What
does she look like?
Cute, elegant?
- Elegant, on the contrary.
A little bit disheveled and
neglected, but very pretty.
- [Crow] Oh no, I
didn't mean you. Sorry.
- Her name's Ann.
- Oh Joe, that's one
of the nicest things
that's ever been said to me.
- Well, I meant it.
I'm really fond of you.
- [Tom] In a one night
stand sort of way.
- You know, when you
leave for New York, here.
So you won't forget
me too quickly.
- [Mike] Get this sweaty
thing off me, you creep.
- But Joe, please don't
let me wait too long.
- [Tom] Ow, that really hurt.
- Come on, I got
12 minutes left.
- What's in 12 minutes?
- My next rendezvous.
- [Tom] Are you attracted
to my Jeff Conaway hair?
- Hello, big boy.
- [Mike] Hello, Jessica Rabbit.
- Well, I'll be darned.
That's not bad either.
Hey, all right.
You really don't know
where to start here.
- [Tom] I tried to tackle my
fidgety sister, but I fell.
- [Crow] I'm Curv E. Voluptuous.
- [Mike] Your body
language is confusing,
you're telling me something...
- [Tom] You need me
to paint your house?
Let me come over there.
- [Crow] Should ee get
our filthy raincoats on
to watch this?
- [Mike] The many loves
of Michael Landon.
- [Tom] An injured member
of the Swedish Bikini Team.
- [Crow] Don't
crush my begonias.
- [Mike] The Horrors
of Spider Island.
- [Tom] I like her
mink tool belt.
- [Crow] Can I look
at you some more?
- [Mike] Just gonna adjust
the bra strap with my teeth.
- [Tom] Settling: the movie.
- [Crow] I checked your
epiglottitis, it's fine.
- [Mike] Hey, try
yourself a she-male, Bob.
- [Tom] Bob really never
follows through on
anything, does he?
- [Crow] Jackie Gleason's
"Music for Lovers Only."
- [Tom] He's going to die
of peroxide inhalation.
- Gladys.
- Oh, you're here.
- What's on your mind?
- Nothing.
- In love?
- [Crow] No, I just
need to prune my chest.
- Mm-hmm.
- You really think that
Bobby's the right man for you?
- [Mike] Well, he attacked me.
- I don't know.
I only know one
thing. I love him.
- [Tom] Well, I
love his groping.
- I hope he doesn't
let you down.
I'd be very sorry for you.
- [Crow] Gosh, I love
Michelle Shocked.
Don't you?
- Hello, Daddy-o.
How about throwing those lamps
on somebody else for change?
- Yeah, baby. Like
you swing too.
- [Mike] All right,
let's check on
your totally
monogamous boyfriend.
Hey!
- [Crow] I rub yeast into
my hair every morning.
- Come on, Gladys.
It's not worth it.
- Don't bother me.
- [Mike] Gingham
spider boyfriend-head
- [Tom] Hey Bob, 50 bucks says
I could beat you arm-wrestling.
- Hey Georgia, get
me a drink too.
- Bobby.
- Yeah?
- Do you have to turn
all the girls' heads?
- Who, me?
They turned mine.
- [Crow] This is the kind of guy
that they warn neighborhoods
about these days.
- Hi, Georgia.
- Hi.
- That dance sure
made me thirsty.
Georgia, aren't you at all
excited about going home soon?
- Kate, let's drink to that.
- Here's to the trip.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
- [Mike] Man, I'd pay $11,000
to be there right now.
- Do you think people are
still talking about us?
- Of course. Now all the
more, since we found you.
- Will the papers
print our story?
- Oh baby.
Will the papers
print your story?
The magazines will
carry your pictures,
and what do you think radio
and TV will do with you?
- [Tom] Make me
show my knockers.
- You'll be amazed
at the reception
you get back in New York.
- Maybe they'll drive
us down Broadway,
with confetti and all.
- [Crow] Hmm, probably not.
- In any case, you've
become a world-famous troop
and who knows, maybe you'll
wind up in Hollywood.
- Oh Bobby, I might make it yet.
- Thank goodness, I still
have a few minutes left.
'Cause my next rendezvous
is very important.
- And this time
who's the lucky one?
- If you won't tell
anyone, Gladys.
- [Mike] And a few Pips.
- Bobby, Gladys is a fine girl.
Up until now, she's
been shy of men.
Please leave her alone.
- Exactly.
I've always yearned
for a girl like this.
- [Tom] What's he doing?
- But I've never found one.
- [Crow] Ever eat glass?
- Why am I telling
you all this anyway?
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- So Mike, if you're a woman
and you're in a plane crash,
you instantly become languid,
helpless and sex-starved,
and you murmur a lot?
- Well, let's just see.
- Okay.
(screaming)
(crashing)
(all groaning)
(murmuring)
- Well, there you have it.
- Yup, survive a plane
crash and you do indeed
become languid and
helpless and sex-starved.
- And you murmur a lot.
Even guys like us.
- Hey, that was fun.
Let's do it again.
- Oh yeah, let's auger
this baby in one more time.
(all screaming)
(instrumental theme music)
(Tom humming)
- [Mike] I'm still needy.
- [Tom] I'm going to marry
an inhibited pork roast.
- Oh Joe, I'm so happy.
- Well, that's what I expected.
- Same old story,
you're nice to a man
and before you know
it, he's getting fresh.
- [Crow] Okay, your turn.
- Ann, I must tell you
something right away. Come on.
- Hey, Ann.
- [Tom] Stop kissing her.
- Let her run.
They're all good for nothing.
They're all the same.
- [Mike] With their big
deal hair and fancy hips.
- Come on, let's have a drink.
- Sure.
- Gladys, it's just
as I told you earlier.
Don't you see that Bob
is just the kind of man
who wants nothing else than
play around with women,
without a single serious
thought in his head.
- You're right, I don't
want to see him again.
- [Tom] Can I let it out?
- Look Bob, you can
keep those remarks
about Ann to yourself, get it?
- [Crow] Ann, Ann, blah
blah blah blah Ann.
(laughing)
- Don't tell me
you're serious, fella.
You haven't fallen for that
little broad, by any chance?
Well, good luck then.
- And what if I were?
- [Mike] Uh, pass.
- Then I'd feel sorry for you.
What are dancers?
Hot goods for cold nights.
Or do you think your
Ann is different?
- For a guy like you,
the worst girl in the
world is too good.
- [Tom] But I like
Tonya Harding.
- [Mike] Oh, thanks.
Now I smell like Midori.
- No, not here. Come on.
- [Crow] Let's take this inside.
- [Tom] My famous
rubber-arm poof punch.
- [Mike] Wait, not here.
Over by the Sung vase.
- [Crow] Ah, he learned
from his master, Moe Howard.
- [Tom] At this
point, I would suggest
the name Spider
Island is misleading.
- [Mike] Ahah! I had
dog doo on my boots.
- [Crow] They're masters
of stage nudging.
(laughing)
- [Tom] (laughing) I'm
bleeding internally.
- [Mike] Oh hi, hair.
- I gotta run, I got a date.
- [Crow] Thanks for touching
my nipple before you left.
- [Tom] Boy, defending
my misogyny really
takes commitment.
- [Mike] Okay see,
this is neither bikini
women nor spiders.
It's really pointless.
- Hah, hah.
- Yeah, he saw an air
molecule that respects women.
- Come on, Gladys.
- Oh, leave me alone, you.
- [Tom] You stole my
drunk filthy boyfriend.
- What's the matter
with you, kid?
Have you gone crazy?
- You ask me that?
No man in this world,
even if he belonged
to your best friend, would
be safe with you around.
- Are you talking about Bobby?
- Who else?
But you can keep him,
I'm through with him.
- I've got news for you.
- [Mike] I'm Clint Howard.
- Bobby just made it
clear to me that you're
the kind of girl that
he's been looking for.
- Do you mean that, Babs?
- If it weren't true, do
you think I'd leave him?
- Babs!
- Go to him. He's
waiting for you.
- [Tom] I'm going to go bench.
- [Mike] Look at that
shadow, it's Sideshow Bob.
- [Crow] Bart.
Still, the movie's better than
"A Midsummer
Night's Sex Comedy."
♪ I don't respect women ♪
♪ Women are just toys for me ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
- [Mike] Say, there's a crotch.
Oh, wrong kind.
- [Crow] The Horrors
of Spider Island.
- [Tom] Boy, these Woman
Hater cigarettes are good.
- [Crow] Soundtrack
by Schroeder.
- [Mike] I'm so lucky
that Bobby went through
a complete personal
transformation in
the last 45 seconds.
- [Tom] Um, where
the hell is he going?
Oh man.
- [Crow] I'm not just wondering
if there's a point
to the movie now.
I'm wondering if there's
a point to anything!
(groaning)
- [Mike] I should move
on to hating older women.
- [Tom] Bobby, what kind of
china shall we register for?
- [Crow] I styled
my hip fur for you.
- [Mike] You better
hurry, he's probably
French-kissing a conch.
- [Crow] And another protagonist
disappears over the horizon.
- [Tom] Christine Todd
Whitman on vacation.
- Bobby.
(gasps)
- [Crow] Finally, the hundreds
of STDs take their toll.
- [Mike] Oh, I see.
So you'd rather
die than marry me.
- [Tom] Someone tattooed
a ball peen hammer on him.
(screaming)
- That was a scream.
- I mean, it was really funny.
(screaming)
- It sounded like Gladys.
- And Bobby's also gone.
- I'll look for them.
You get dressed and follow me.
- [Tom] No, undressed.
What is he thinking?
- [Mike] Yes?
♪ Spider spider spider ♪
- [Tom] Ooh, spider
shin splints.
- [Crow] He's got less
back hair as a spider.
- [Tom] Pay no attention,
I'm just an outcropping.
- [Mike] I wonder if
my Lightdays with wings
will actually get me airborne.
- [Tom] When did Duke
Ellington do this soundtrack?
- [Crow] Now with my
spider-like grace.
- [Mike] Oh man, this is hard.
- [Tom] Hey, a pod
of exotic dancers.
- [Mike] Don't you want to
see my segmented thorax?
(gun clicking)
- [Crow] Dang potato gun.
- You go up ahead and
try and help Gladys,
I'll go back and
get the ammunition.
Quick!
- [Tom] I really like spiders.
I never did any experiments
on them in school.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Oh, thank you, movie.
- [Crow] Sweet.
- Nice.
- [Crow] I get her lip wax.
- [Tom] How does this movie
really feel about
women, I wonder?
- [Mike] I'll be right back,
I think I got something
that can help.
- [Tom] Another
character flees the film.
- Bob!
- [Crow] Do you
have a breath mint?
- [Tom] Oh, I guess I'll
reload the boat then.
- Bobby.
- [Mike] Geez, will he
tell God I punched him?
- [Crow] I'm a
sprite again, wheee.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] I'm gonna kick the
crap out of you, come on.
- [Mike] I thought
spiders were supposed to
go scurrying under the
bathtub when they saw us.
- [Crow] I'm gonna pick you
up and throw you into my web,
which I made with machine
tools in my garage.
- [Tom] What was that exchange?
- [Mike] Look, whoever you are.
I got these spiders I
need to deal with, hey.
(instrumental theme music)
- Where are the bullets?
Here.
- [Crow] Hey, you stepped
on my web, you jerk.
- [Tom] What, are ya
scared of a spider?
Come on out here.
- [Mike] I had a garden
spider do this to me once.
Hid in my bathroom
and called the police.
- [Crow] I want Joe Frazier.
- [Tom] Maybe I've always
just misunderstood
what spiders are.
They're large, hairy
bipeds with pants.
(whimpering)
- [Mike] Good, Georgia,
keep distracting him
while I think of something.
- Gary.
- [Crow] Yep, you got me.
- [Tom] Oh man.
Now it just seems
kind of stupid.
- [Mike] I'm glad it's dark.
You know, I can imagine
my own action scene.
- [Crow] Try saying
"Gary" to him.
- [Tom] Oh man, my spinnerets
back into my pants.
That doesn't do any good.
- Uh-huh, uh-huh.
- [Mike] Oh, that's a shame.
- [Crow] Come on,
sunshine. Come on.
(monster growling)
(choking)
(screaming)
- [Tom] Hey, there's
more pretzel sticks.
(growling)
- [Mike] Um, Larry,
Harry, Barry-
What the hell is it?
(fearful whimpering)
- [Crow] I have a good
mind to put this up my butt
and entertain at Lollapalooza.
- [Mike] Let's take
the cabin, men.
- Wait, each of you take a
torch and we'll take him.
We can only destroy
him with fire.
Here.
- [Tom] Remind me why
we're listening to you.
Let's just check
in as to who was
getting his butt kicked by
a spider and who wasn't,
- All right, come on.
Come on.
We must go on.
Two of you take that
path over there,
you go through the bushes.
The rest of you come with me.
No one should go alone,
always go in pairs.
Come on.
- [Crow] So go alone and panic?
Is that what you said?
- [Mike] This is
good chase music.
- [Crow] Suddenly I want
to do the Charleston.
♪ Gary, Gary ♪
♪ Gary ♪
- [Mike] The paparazzi!
- [Tom] Oh Cindy,
your torch is so cute.
I just can't wear a torch.
- Come on, he's over there.
- [Tom] Man, I would love to
be chased by these villagers.
- [Crow] Yeah, that'd be great.
Surrounded, beaten and burnt.
- [Tom] No no, that's
not what I meant.
- [Crow] That's just
my thing, I guess.
- [Mike] Please,
please let me live.
I'll eat aphids off your
rose bushes, I promise.
- [Tom] So, is he strong?
- [Crow] Hey, listen bub,
he's got radioactive blood!
- [Mike] Whoa, hey.
- [Crow] It just ticks me off.
- [Mike] Is this the
titillation trump card
we're seeing here, dancers
chasing a half-man half-spider?
- [Tom] I do prefer
the sweaty lounging
and beefy spooning,
the way there was
almost nudity there
a couple of times.
- [Crow] Shoot, I usually
retreat to my little hole
in the barn and climb up
my string to the rafters.
- [Mike] Uh, we're over here.
- [Tom] The whole movie just
up and ran away from us.
- [Crow] Well, I'm going
to go on break, Mike.
It's been 10 years,
I think I'm owed one
You cover me?
- [Tom] Can he do that?
- [Mike] They need
a big shirtless bird
to come in and
scoop up the spider.
- Maybe we've lost him.
- [Tom] They will not come
if I build it, shut up.
- [Mike] You know,
the Dukes of Dixieland
also did the "Psycho"
soundtrack, I think.
- [Crow] I'm back,
I feel much better.
(Tom chanting in Latin)
You should take a break.
- Stop! The quicksand
starts here.
- [Crow] Oh, right. The
quicksand, remember?
- [Tom] I'm sterile,
don't touch me.
- [Mike] Ah, I skitter lightly
across the top of the mud.
- [Tom] Distributing my weight
evenly over my eight legs.
Making my weight delicately...
- [Crow] Can't I just
leave with dignity? Oh...
- [Mike] Okay, so
I'm no water spider.
- [Tom] I hid egg
sacs in your luggage!
(screaming)
- Better dead than
continue living.
- [Crow] As a general
rule, I'm not sure I agree.
- [Mike] Wow, he
found out too late
that Coco Wheats can't be beat.
- [Tom] Now they gotta stop
at Praying Mantis
Island for supplies.
- [Crow] The bad news is
they were picked
up by Captain Ron.
- [Tom] Shrimp
kebabs, shrimp gumbo,
shrimp ice cream,
shrimpskin coats,
shrimp hubcaps,
shrimp contact lenses,
shrimp-based religion.
- Okay.
I can't believe we ran around
in our underwear so much.
- Come on, girls. Babs, Kate.
- [Crow] I want to sleep
on a bed of breasts.
- [Mike] So anyway,
that was my experience
on the island with the girls
when I became a spider.
Did it teach me anything?
Maybe not, but you
know, in the end, hey!
- [Tom] So, you want to end
your movie that way, huh?
Okay. Get bent,
we're outta here.
- [Crow] Shrimp
personal watercraft.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Hey, turkey legs.
- Hey, bloaty!
- I'm gonna make myself a
braunschweiger melt, you in?
- You know it!
(growling)
Uh-oh.
- Hi, uh, monster.
- Who is clearly Mike.
- Ew, What happened, Mike?
- Ah, I got bit
by a giant spider
on my way in from the theater,
so now I'm a giant spider.
- Yeah. You're gonna see that.
Yeah, I gotta say though, Mike,
you look even less like a spider
than that guy Gary
did in the movie.
- Yeah.
- You think so?
- yeah, you're still
like 99.99999999% human.
- No, I'm a, I'm a huge spider.
I got this giant spider claw.
- So. What?
You're going to
attack us with that
and drain out our
essential life fluids or?
- No!
In fact, I was going to make
myself a braunschweiger melt.
- Now that's a coincidence!
(exaggerated laughing)
(sighing)
- Let's see what Pearl's up to.
The castle's gone.
There's nothing but
a huge dark stain
from them blasting off.
- Ah, no Mike, the
stain's from Bobo.
(laughing)
- Oh, sorry Nelson, forgot to
tell you we're moving back.
They had some weird
arcane law in that town
about not throwing
garbage out your windows,
and I cannot abide that
kind of oppression.
So we got the castle back
up on the flatbed out there.
We had to stop and diesel up
at this here Pump 'N Munch.
Bobo's in the men's
room, me and Brain Guy
are here in the ladies room.
- Oh, I had no idea.
- Right...
- Lawgiver, Brain Guy, look!
I found a bunch of balloons
in the men's room
vending machine,
so I bought us a whole bunch.
Look, they're
individually wrapped.
Well, this one even
protects us from something.
Oh, this one is from France
and it's supposed to tickle.
(awkward laughing)
And this one, this
is a ribbed balloon
that's supposed to
make some lady happy.
I really don't understand.
- Can I see those please?
- Bobo, we need to
have a little talk.
You're not ready
for this, Nelson.
Now Bobo, when a flower
loves a bee very much...
- Oh, my many lady friends
will appreciate my caution.
- [Bobo] Oooh! Really?
(somber theme music)
(Bobo exclaiming)
(women screaming)